warofangels.net 2012-06-13

# Official War of Angels Global Site

    This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you and how we may use them. This Privacy Policy may be revised without notice and will become effective upon posting on this site.
    
    **How Neowiz Games Uses Your Personal Information.**
    This policy covers how Neowiz Games Corporation (“Neowiz Games”) treats personal information that it collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, or email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
    
    **This privacy policy only applies to Neowiz Games.**
    This policy does not apply to Neowiz Game’s affiliates, subsidiaries, and the practices of companies that Neowiz Games does not own or control or to people that Neowiz Games does not employ or manage.
    
    **Information Collection and Use.**
    Neowiz Games may collect personal information when you register with Neowiz Games. When you register we will ask you to input your e-mail address, which it will become your user name and create a password (collectively “User ID”), and may ask for information such as your name, home address, phone number, email address, Twitter® credentials, Facebook® credentials, and/or friends or referrals on the Neowiz Games network. In addition, when purchasing products or services, you will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number, expiration date, and billing addresses. 
    
    When you register with Neowiz Games by creating a User ID and password, we may ask additional information such as your date of birth (age), and gender. Additionally, after you register and sign in to our services, certain information that you provide are not anonymous to us: a registered user has the capability to search for another Neowiz Games registered user on Twitter® or Facebook®. Please note that Neowiz Games may store the personal information that we collect from you and these information will allow us to inform you about our products and services (including Neowiz Games sponsored marketing activities), upgrades, to provide technical/order support regarding your use of our service. In addition, we may use the personal information internally to conduct research and evaluation to enhance our service to you. 
    
    Neowiz Games and third parties may collectively coordinate together to improve our services and products, and conduct market research. We may also provide your personal information to other companies that may offer related products and/or services. If so, we will notify you that the information will be shared and provide you with an opportunity to opt-out. We provide the personal information to trusted partners, including third party publishers, who work with Neowiz Games and they do not use the information for any other purpose, and those entities must oblige and maintain the confidentiality. 
    
    Additionally, your personal information may be assigned or transferred to third party assignees in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, reorganization, or other similar changes Neowiz Games’ corporate structure. If such even occurs, we will notify appropriate information regarding the change to users who have provided us with his/her e-mail address. 
    
    Lastly, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required by law, instances including but not limited to, responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In addition, we may disclose the information if we reasonably believe it is necessary to share information to investigate, prevent, or bring legal action against you if you are suspected of conducting illegal activities, violate the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other Service of Use Agreements for Neowiz Games or its products that causes injury to us and/or to other users. 
    
    Under the California law, if you are a legal resident of the State of California, you may request information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to third parties. As discussed above, we do not disclose or share your personal information with third party companies without your consent. If you wish to opt out to prevent your personal information from being disclosed or shared with third parties and/or receiving information from Neowiz Games regarding our products, services, or promotions, please contact us at:
    
    Neowiz Games Corporation
    Attn: Customer Support - Privacy Policy Issues 
    Neowiz Tower, 192-2, Gumi-dong, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si,Gyeonggi-do, 
    Korea 463-870
    
    You may also contact us by e-mail at:
    [help@warofangles.net](mailto:help@warofangles.net)(War of Angels)
    Or 
    [help@sevensoulsonline.com](mailto:help@sevensoulsonline.com)(Seven Souls Online)

    **Payment Information.**
    For payment transactions, Neowiz Games may provide you with method(s) to allow you to make transactions in our store through one of our Payment Gateway (“PG”) partners. During the payment process, you will be assigned a unique code (“PG Code”) created by one of our PG partners. Your assigned PG Code will be confirmed once you complete your first transaction. Once you have been assigned a PG Code, your payment information is stored in the PG system. All subscriptions paid through these third parties are subject to their Terms of Service, and we will not be responsible for any terms and conditions contained therein. Please refer to the Payment Terms of Use  for more information (the Payment Terms of Use will be uploaded when the users are authorized to initiate the payment process in the future). 
    
    **Cookies on Neowiz Games.**
    Cookies are small bits of information sent by a host that is stored on your hard disk by your computer’s browser. Cookies speed up your online usage by remembering your personal information such as your User ID (your e-mail address and/or password), and gather your online activities data for marketing or promotional purposes.
    
    You may disable cookies from Neowiz Games on your browser. However, each browser has its unique cookies preference setting so please refer to your browser for more information.
    
    **Minors Under the Age of 13.**
    We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. NO ONE UNDER THE AGE OF 13 MAY PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, PLEASE DO NOT ATTEMPT TO REGISTER OR SEND ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF TO US, INCLUDING YOUR NAME, ADDRESS, TELEPHONE NUMBER, AND/OR EMAIL ADDRESS. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact the Privacy Policy department at:
    
    [help@warofangles.net](mailto:help@warofangles.net)(War of Angels)
    Or 
    [help@sevensoulsonline.com](mailto:help@sevensoulsonline.com)(Seven Souls Online)
    
    **Mature Themes in Online Games Serviced by Neowiz Games.**
    Please be advised that due to mature/adult themes in certain online games serviced by Neowiz Games, Neowiz Games may require minors to agree to adult supervision, including, but not limited to, authorization from the minor’s guardian, and/or if those minors do not satisfy the minimum age requirements, they may be prohibited from playing those games. We will post the age requirement notice on each of our games that we service.
    
    **Confidentiality.**
    We limit access to personal information about you to certain employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you. 

    **If you have questions, suggestions, or wish to file a complaint, please contact us at:**
    Neowiz Games Corporation
    Customer Support - Privacy Policy Issues 
    Neowiz Tower, 192-2, Gumi-dong, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si,Gyeonggi-do, 
    Korea 463-870
    
    [help@warofangles.net](mailto:help@warofangles.net)(War of Angels)
    Or 
    [help@sevensoulsonline.com](mailto:help@sevensoulsonline.com)(Seven Souls Online)
    
    Effective Date: [October 1, 2010]
    Last Updated: January 16, 2012
    
    Copyright © 2012 Neowiz Games Corporation. All Rights Reserved. Pmang and Neowiz Games Corporation are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Neowiz Games Corporation in Korea, and/or other countries.
